Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory8 Mss.B.B61.inventory08
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents L
  - Lewis, Albert B. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 May 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 May 23
  - Lewis, C.I. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 19; 1p.
  - Lewis, C.M. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Gellner-Woltmann, M. Aug. 15, 1933), 1934 Jan. 23; 1p.
  - Lewis, Charles F. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 24; 1p.
  - Lewis, Franklin C. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 May 20
    - From Boas, 1909 May 24; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 27
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 30; postc.
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 May 11
    - To Boas, 1909 May 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 19; 1p.
  - Lewis, Frederic T. (Box 56)
    - F.T. Lewis -- to E.A. Hooten, 1937 Sept. 25; 1p.
  - Lewis, I. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 3
  - Lewis, Joseph (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - J. Lewis -- from N. Michelson, 1938 Jan. 26
  - Lewis, Read (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 1; 1p.
  - Lewis, S.C. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 29
  - Lewis, T.W. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p.
  - Lewis, William S. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 27; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 1
  - Lewisohn, Adolph (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 13
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 13; 1p.
  - Lewy?? (Box 56)
    - Lewy? -- to R. Thurnwald, 1936 Oct. 26; 2p.
  - Lewy?? C. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 14; 1p.
  - Lewy, Ernst (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 18; 4p.
  - Lewy, Fritz (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 27; 2p.
  - Lewy, Julius (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1933 July 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 16; 2p.
  - Ley (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 20
  - Leyen, F. von der (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 27; 1p.
  - Leyh? (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1888? Apr. 7
  - Lhuccia?, P.W. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Li, Fang-Kuei (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec.; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec.; 2p.
    - Fang-Kuei Li -- to E. Sapir, 1937 Feb. 14; 1p.
  - Liagre, A. de (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: Nederlandsch Comité tot onderzoek van de Ooorszaken van den Wereldoorlog., Nov. 1924.)
  - Liard (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 4
  - Liberal and Labor Committee (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 19; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. end
      (See Blanchard, Paul)
  - Liberal Education and Democracy (Box 56)
    - Enc. with Boas, F. to Greene, T.M., Feb. 17, 1941.
  - Liberman, Maurice (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 7; 1p.
      (On margin: Boas, F. to Klineberg,)
  - Libman, E. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 11; 1p.
  - Librairie Félix Alcan (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p.
  - Library of Congress (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From W.A. Slade, 1927 Mar. 7
    - (Enc. with Farnum, J.L., Mar. 8, 1927)
  - Lichtenberg, Evelyn (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 14; 1p.
  - Lichtenstein, Paul (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 1; 2p.
  - Lichtenstein, Walter (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Aug. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 23
    - (See: BalliviC!n, A. 's letter to him of same date.), 1918 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 8; 2p.
    - W. Lichtenstein -- to W. Austen, 1918 May 1; 3p.
    - W. Lichtenstein -- from A. BalliviC!n, 1918 Apr. 23; 1p.
  - Lichtmann, M.M. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 24; 1p.
  - Lickley, R.W. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Lieber, Hugo (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - (Enc: Wettstein, R. to Beck, Carl Nov. 14, 1920), 1921 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 1p.
  - Lieberman, Elias (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1942 July 3; 1p.
  - Liebman?, Henry L.? (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 15; 1p.
  - Liebman, Laura (Box 56)
    - See Hendley, C.J., Dec. 24, 1937.
  - Liebowitz, Ben (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23; radiogram
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 25; cablegram
    - From Boas, 1933 May 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 31; cablegram
    - From Boas, 1933 June 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 6; telegram
    - To Boas, 1933 May 9; Cablegram
    - To Boas, 1933 May 20; radiogram
    - To Boas, 1933 May 23; radiogram
    - To Boas, 1933 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 6; radiogram
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; cablegram
    - To Boas, 1933 July 12; 8p.
    - B. Liebowitz -- to E. Boas, 1933 May 4; 10p.
    - (Enc: Rosenfeld, L. to Szilard Schlesinger, K. to szilard Szilard to Beveridge, W., Apr. 24, May 2, 1933 May 2, 1933 May 4, 1933)
  - Liégeois, C. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 20; 1p.
  - Liekens, E. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Lienex, J.D. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 20
  - Lier, Saniano de (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1941 June 15; 1p.
  - Lieson, W.A. co. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1934 May 11; bill
  - Liestol, K. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas
      See Sydow, C.M. to Germany. Reichsu. Presussischen Minister für Wissenshaft, Erziehung und Volksbildung.
      - (Enc. with Sydow, C.M., Mar. 1, 1935)
  - Liggett, Mrs. N.W. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
  - Likert, R. (Box 56)
    - Enc. with Murphy, G. to Bonbright, J.C., Oct. 16, 1929.
  - Lilian (Box 56)
    See Reichard, Lilian J.
  - Lilienthatl, Reinhold von (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p.
  - Liljestrand, G. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 14; 1p.
  - Lillie, Frank R. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - F.R. Lillie -- from M. Mead, 1926 Jan. 6
  - Lillie, Ralph S. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; telegram
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p.
  - Lilling, E.W. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 15; 2p.
  - Lincer, William (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 6; 1p.
  - Lincoln, G.I. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 27; 1p.
  - Lincoln, Helen (Box 56)
    - H. Lincoln -- to R.W. Bryan, 1932 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Lincoln, Waldo (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 19
  - Lindblom, Gerhard (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 2; 1p.
  - Lindeman, E.C. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 26; 1p.
    - (Enc: List of organizations invited to cooperate) on McNaboe resolution), 1936 July 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 30; 1p.
  - Lindemann, M. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1882 Dec. 21; postcard
    - To Boas, 1885 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 7; postcard
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 2; postcard
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1886 July 8; postcard
    - M. Lindemann -- to Toni Boas for F.B., 1884 Oct. 14
  - Lindgren, Albert? John (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 21; 1p.
  - Lindley, E.H. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 4; telegr.
  - Lindlof, J.M. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 6; 1p.
  - Lindsey, Edward S. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 16
  - Linfield, H.S. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 27; 1p.
  - Ling, G.H. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 16
  - Ling Nan Univ. Trustees (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 21; 1p.
  - Lingg, Claire (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 5; 1p.
  - Linguistic Society of America (Box 56)
    - From R.G. Kent, 1925 Jan. 12
    - From R.G. Kent, 1925 Jan. 10
    - From R.G. Kent, 1925 Feb. 14
    - From R.G. Kent, 1925 Sept. 28
    - From R.G. Kent, 1925 Nov. 30
    - From R.G. Kent, 1925 Nov. 30
    - (Minutes & constitution Enc. with Kent, R.C. Jan. 12, 1925.), 1928 July-Aug.
    - (Enc. with Sturtevant, E.H. Sept. 26, 1927), 1937 May 1
    - (Regulations - Enc. with Kent Jan. 22, 1940), 1937 May 1; 1p.
      (Resolutions)
    - See American Anthropological Assn. Comm. on Amer. Indian Linguistics., Apr. 25-26, 1937)
    - See Kent, R.G., Jan. 9, 1928.
    - Proposal, n.d.
  - Linscheid, G.A. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas
      (On margin: Boas, F. to Linscheid, G.A. Mar. 15, 1928)
  - Linton, E.B. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Linton, Ralph (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1917 Sept. 14
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 11
    - To Boas, 1919 June 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - R. Linton -- from E.P. Boas, 1943 Feb. 10
    - R. Linton -- to L.P. Eisenhart, 1943 Jan. 2; 1p.
  - Linville, H.R. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept.
    - (Enc. originally with Linville, H.R. Oct. 21, 1926 and filed with it under Oct. 21, 1926), 1926 Oct. 21; 2p.
    - (Enc: Linville, H.R. Reaping the whirlwind. Sept. 1926), 1929 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - (Enc: Linville, H.R. to Ryan, G.J., Jan. 19, 1929)
    - See Lindeman, E., June 26, 1936.
    - H.R. Linville -- to G.J. Ryan, 1929 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - (Enc. originally with Linville, H.R., Jan. 21, 1929)
  - Lipkind, William (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. (open Letter) Nov. 6, 1941., 1942 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 30; 2p.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter) May 10, 1940., 1942 Feb. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 May 31; 1p.
    - W. Lipkind -- to Mrs. Urbach, 1939 May 30; 1p.
  - Lipman, Anni (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec.; 5p.
  - Lipmann, Otto (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3; 1p.
  - Lippe, D. von der (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 7; 3p.
  - Lippe, Frau von der (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1893 Feb. 20; 3p.
  - Lippincott, B. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1934 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 8; 1p.
  - Lippincott, J.B. Co. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 2; 1p.
  - Lippman, W. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 14
  - Lips, Julius E. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 8; telegram
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 July 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 12; 3p.
    - (Enc: List of his publications), 1934 Feb. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 31; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - See Enc. Boas, F. to Moe, H.A., Dec. 31, 1936.
    - See Stieglitz, Leo. Dec. 1936, 1937 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 15; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 30; 3p.
    - See Heath, D.C. & Co. Oct. 31, 1938., 1938 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 end; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 8; 3p.
    - J.E. Lips -- from Anon., 1933 Apr. 28
    - (Enc. with Rivet, P., May 13, 1933.)
    - J.E. Lips -- to L.I. Dublin, 1937 Dec. 1; 2p.
    - J.E. Lips -- from Eckert, 1933 May 2
    - (Enc. with Rivet, P., May 13, 1933)
    - J.E. Lips -- from F.D. Fackenthal, 1934 Oct. 26
    - (Enc. with Fackenthal, F.D., Oct. 26, 1934
    - J.E. Lips -- from K.N. Llewellyn, 1935 June 21
    - J.E. Lips -- from Walter Mueller, 1939 Dec. 13
    - J.E. Lips -- to Otto Sattler, 1939 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - J.E. Lips -- to E. v. Schroetter, 1939 Dec. 12; 1p.
  - Lipschitz, Dr. A.S. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 1; 1p.
  - Lischner, H. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 May 3
    - From Boas, 1909 May 20
    - From Boas, 1909 June 23
    - From Boas, 1909 June 29
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 20; 2p.
  - Lissauer, Dr. Max J. (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1898 May 4
    - M.J. Lissauer -- to Emil L. Boas, 1904 June 20; 1p.
  - List of doctors in anthropology (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan.; 1p.
  - List of linguistic material collected (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec.; 3p.
  - List of names (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1938 end; 1p.
  - List of reprints sent out (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 20; 1p.
  - Lister, Walter (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 25; 1p.
  - Lit? Jacques (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 31
  - Littauer, L.N. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 14; 1p.
  - Littauer, Rudolf (Box 56)
    - See Notgeme inschaft deutscher Wissen-schaftler i m Ausland Minutes., 1938 Nov. 10
  - Little, J.J. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 13; 1p.
  - The Little Temple (Box 56)
    See Habas, Ralph A.
  - Litvinoff, M. (Box 56)
    - M. Litvinoff -- to F. Nansen, 1926 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - M. Litvinoff -- from F. Nansen, 1926 Aug. 31
  - Livi, Ridolfo (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 28; 4p.
  - Livi, Mrs. Ridolfo (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p.
  - Office of Living Age (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 29
  - Livingston, Arthur (Box 56)
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 4
  - Livingston, Burton E. (Box 56)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - (Enc: Resolution for the A.A.A.S. re publications for foreign societies and libraries.), 1931 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p.
    - (Enc: Resolution), 1920 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 1; telegram
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 2p.
    - B.E. Livingston, -- to R.W. Bryan, 1931 Jan. 5; 1p.
  - Llewellyn, Karl N. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Executive power and administration among American Indians.), 1933 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 July 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, Feb. 11, 1937.
    - K.N. Llewellyn -- to J. Lips, 1935 June 21; 1p.
  - Lloyd, John Uri (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p.
  - Lloyd, Lola Maverick (Box 57)
    - See Catt, C.C., Feb. 10, 1937.
  - Loba, G. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 28
  - Loch, R.A. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 4
  - Lochard, Metz T.P. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p.
  - Lochner, L.P. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1917 June 18
  - Locke, A.L. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - A.L. Locke -- from E.J. Scott, 1925 Dec. 10
    - A.L. Locke -- to C.G. Woodson
      - (Enc. with Woodson, C.G., Nov. 16,1926)
  - Lockemann, T. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 16; 1p.
  - Lockwood (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1916 May 26
  - Lodge, G. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 10; 1p.
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 29; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 4; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 4
  - Lods, Adolph (Box 57)
    - See Anon to Mond, Robert, Mar. 5, 1937.
      General note
      "French Spirit Against Racism
  - Loeb, Irma H. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 2; 2p.
  - Loeb, Jacques (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 24; 2p.
  - Loeb, Morris (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 6; 2p.
  - Loeffler, F. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 21; 1p.
  - Loevi, J. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 18; 1p.
  - Loewe, F. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1933 May 15; 4p.
  - Loewe, Victor (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
  - Loewenstein, Hubertus (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 2; 1p.
  - Logan, F.L. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
  - Logan, R.W. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p.
  - Loggie,? T.G. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 24; 2p.
  - Lohmann, E. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - E. Lohmann -- from K. Schneider, 1933 June 28
  - Löhnberg, E. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 1; 4p.
  - Lohstaeter, Friedrich (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 24; 2p.
  - Loiseawe, H. (Box 57)
    - H. Loiseawe -- to Barnard College. Comm. on Instruction, 1923 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Lombard, Warren P. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1896 July 29
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p.
  - Lombardo, Carmyn J. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 14; 1p.
  - Lombardo, M.D. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1912 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 21
  - London, H. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 7
  - London Times (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 2p.
  - Lónez, José -- (see also López, José) (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1911 Aug. 29; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 July 7; telegram
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 1; 4p.
  - Long, H.H. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 15; 1p.
  - Long, W.W. (Box 57)
    - W.W. Long -- from F.M. Olbrechts, 1935 Apr. 23
  - Loomis, M.E. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 10; 1p.
  - Loomis, Mrs. R.S. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 4; postcard
  - Lopatin, I.A. (Box 57)